Jahziel Villasana-Espinoza

4888 Duncan Wood Dr., 30096, Duluth, Georgia US

Jahziel loves programming computers. He's especially interested in systems programming, building and specifying the Open Web, and teaching.

Programming Languages The Web! Source Control javascript go c python node.js react redux jekyll git github c# java Databases Linux/Unix sqlite sql server dynamodb WORK EXPERIENCE (2)

WORK EXPERIENCE (2)

Software Engineering Intern State Farm May 2019 - Current

Atlanta, (US) Georgia

Joined a small Enterprise Technology team that maintains several microservices and APIs for the Claims side of State Farm's business, using Spring, Node.js, and AWS.

Co-op Engineer Yokogawa Corp. of America August 2017 - May 2019

♥ Newnan, (US) Georgia

- Developed .NET apps for a variety of departments with focus on streamlining and automating existing business processes
- Developed an Android app that streamlines plant tours, with estimated savings in engineering time of more than \$10,000 per year

EDUCATION (1)

B.S Computer Science Georgia Institute of Technology

2015 - 2020

cs1332: data structures and algorithms cs2110: computer organization and programming: assembly and c cs2200: intro to systems and networking cs3210: operating system design cs4240: compilers and interpreters capstone project

GPA: 3.43

LANGUAGES

English
Native speaker

Spanish
Native speaker

PROJECTS

MDN JS Docs

Documenting recent ECMAScript features on MDN. Tasks include updating compat data, writing interactive examples, and writing entire reference pages with the help of various standards specification documents.

javascript ecmascript mdn documentation standards

Ankiport

A web app that converts Quizlets to Anki decks.

javascript react flask

newpost

A little CLI that lets you create new GH Pages/Jekyl blog post files with ease.



resumic

A standardized JSON schema for your resume, with a CLI to generate beautiful resumes from your data.



jahz.co

My personal website and blog.



CS2110 Final Assignment: C memory library

Implemented the C dynamic memory allocation library (malloc, calloc, realloc, free).

